hdrmaps.com 2018-10-28

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how HDRMAPS uses and protects any information that you give HDRMAPS when you use this website. HDRMAPS is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. HDRMAPS may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

## What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * name
  * contact information including email address
  * your billing and additional addresses 
  * your comments and reviews to products or blog articles

For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.

## What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * we use customer data only to setup order invoice if it's needed

## Our Blog

You should avoid entering personally identifiable information to the actual comment field of any blog post comments that you submit on this website. Your comment and it’s associated personal data will remain on this site until we see fit to either  **1.)**  remove the comment or  **2.)**  remove the blog post. Should you wish to have the comment and it’s associated personal data deleted, please [email us here](mailto:contact@hdrmaps.com) using the email address that you commented with.

If you are under 16 years of age you  **MUST**  obtain parental consent before posting a comment on our blog.

**NOTE:**  You should avoid entering personally identifiable information to the actual comment field of any blog post comments that you submit on this website.

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## About this website's server

This website is hosted by OVH within a France data centre located in Roubaix.  
Activity both within and outside of the datacentres is monitored and recorded on secure servers, with surveillance teams working on site, 24/7. Learn more about security in OVH

All personal data  between this website and your browser is encrypted and delivered over [HTTPS](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTPS "Learn more on Wiki").

## Site visitation tracking

Like most websites, this site uses Google Analytics (GA) to track user interaction. We use this data to determine the number of people using our site, to better understand how they find and use our web pages and to see their journey through the website.

Although GA records data such as your geographical location, device, internet browser and operating system, none of this information personally identifies you to us. GA also records your computer’s IP address which could be used to personally identify you but Google do not grant us access to this. We consider Google to be a third party data processor (see [section 6.0](https://www.fellowshipproductions.co.uk/privacy-policy/#data-processors) below).

GA makes use of cookies, details of which can be found on [Google’s developer guides](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage). FYI our website uses the analytics.js implementation of GA.

Disabling cookies on your internet browser will stop GA from tracking any part of your visit to pages within this website.

## Our Third Party Data Processors

  * Google ([Privacy policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en-GB/policies/privacy/))
  * Facebook ([Data policy](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php "Learn more"))

## Data breaches

We will report any unlawful data breach of this website’s database or the database(s) of any of our third party data processors to any and all relevant persons and authorities within 72 hours of the breach if it is apparent that personal data stored in an identifiable manner has been stolen.

## Data controller

The data controller of this website is: HDRMAPS,  company operating as a proprietorship.

Whose registered office is:  
Ul. Jabłońska 17  
57-430 Jugów  
Poland

## Data protection officer

Email: contact@hdrmaps.com

## Email newsletter

If you choose to join our email newsletter, the email address that you submit will be stored within this website’s own database.  
Your email address will remain database until you specifically request removal from the list.   
You can do this by unsubscribing using the unsubscribe links contained in any email newsletters that we send you or by requesting removal via Newsletter Subscription managment [here](https://hdrmaps.com/newsletter/manage/ "Manage newsletter")

## How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

## Contact forms and email links

Should you choose to contact us using the contact form on our [Contact Us](http://hdrmaps.com/contact "Contact Us") page or an email link like this one, none of the data that you supply will be stored by this website or passed to / be processed by any of the third party data processors. Not all mail servers are secured. Therefore, we would suggest that you always consider email as an insecure medium and not include personal, confidential or otherwise sensitive information within an email.

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Controlling your personal information

You can anytime delete your account. For this you need to log-in [here](https://hdrmaps.com/customer/account/ "Log in") using your login and password and click [Delete Account](https://hdrmaps.com/selfdelete/customer/index/ "delete account"). All your pending and canceled orders will be deleted within a week. All completed orders will still remain in our database for Internal record keeping.  
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.   
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

## List of cookies we collect

The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.

COOKIE name| COOKIE Description  
---|---  
CART | The association with your shopping cart.  
CATEGORY_INFO | Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.  
COMPARE | The items that you have in the Compare Products list.  
CURRENCY | Your preferred currency  
CUSTOMER | An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.  
CUSTOMER_AUTH | An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.  
CUSTOMER_INFO | An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.  
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS | Stores the Customer Segment ID  
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE | A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.  
FRONTEND | You sesssion ID on the server.  
GUEST-VIEW | Allows guests to edit their orders.  
LAST_CATEGORY | The last category you visited.  
LAST_PRODUCT | The most recent product you have viewed.  
NEWMESSAGE | Indicates whether a new message has been received.  
NO_CACHE | Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.  
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART | A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.  
POLL | The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.  
POLLN | Information on what polls you have voted on.  
RECENTLYCOMPARED | The items that you have recently compared.  
STF | Information on products you have emailed to friends.  
STORE | The store view or language you have selected.  
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE | Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.  
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS | The products that you have recently viewed.  
WISHLIST | An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.  
WISHLIST_CNT | The number of items in your Wishlist.  
JM_TREX_TPL | Template settings  
COOKIEALERTCLOSEDFLAG, COOKIEALERTSTATE | Cookies storing Cookies and Policy warning at bottom of page  
  
Keep in mind that there are also cookies from Google and Facebook. We use Google Analytics and Facebook for login service.
